{"data":[{"question":"What ________ is it? It's half past six.","a":"color","b":"time","c":"name","d":"box","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use \"what's the time? or what time is it?\" to ask for time\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"How many ________ are there on the ceiling?","a":"clock","b":"maps","c":"lights","d":"picture","answer":"3","explain":"\n- How many + countable plural nouns","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"How many erasers are there on her ________?","a":"desk","b":"wall","c":"chairs","d":"room","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We often put eraser on desk.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"What's your sister doing? She's ________ a book.","a":"singing","b":"reading","c":"teaching","d":"ringing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We often say read book","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The ________ shoes are Peter's.","a":"bus","b":"blouse","c":"both","d":"brown","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Brown: used as a adjective of color","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Your ________ are new, Paul.","a":"shirt","b":"blouse","c":"trousers","d":"hat","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Trousers: Is the only plural noun, others are singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"There are ________ boys in our class.","a":"no","b":"not","c":"none","d":"no of","answer":"1","explain":"- No: used as a determiner followed by a noun (means not any)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Is Susan ________ home?","a":"on","b":"at","c":"in","d":"into","answer":"2","explain":"\n- At home: in your house and not being outside","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Shall ________ go for a walk?","a":"us","b":"we","c":"you","d":"me","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Shall I\/we...?: used to make a suggestion, or ask a question that you want the other person to decide about.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"It is a quarter ________ one.","a":"over","b":"pass","c":"past","d":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past (prep): later than a particular time.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}